Shibuya SARAH
Yu Hamada
Zaücklich
I wonder where they went.
Finish pork belly
Fukusono ni
Extension
conhecer
Delicious!
And really tender!
Really vivacious and so beautiful!
Hot, all the time loving!
Delicious!
Gelato in the arms of a flower
I'm at the end of the gelato.
Where to next?
But still atz
I don't know.
But you know what? I want some sar-ta-antanee.
I'm dying to try it!
I just looked it up and there are so many different flavors.
I looked it up in one.
That's all I found.
Wait, I know what Genie said.
What's that?
Sauter Antanee.
That looks so good.
Let's go here. Let's go where?
Maybe we'll find out when we get back to the other side.Maybe we'll find out when we get back over there.
Stay tuned for the next video!
I'm making the rounds of the beer shops in Dataran right now, but my leads are too few and far between.
Plus, I was thinking of going to the place where Mr. Generations went.
Yes, it looks like we'll be seeing two of them.
Yes, they are.
They came out here, too, right?
Right here?
Right here.
It's interesting to see now, but it's even better in the toaster.
It's almost like it's freshly made, and you can even serve it hot.
It's so good!
Sesame seeds are also recommended.
Delicious with sesame seeds!
Everyone can enjoy eating sesame!
The taste of sesame
I'm glad I'm someone who understands
The smell of black sesame
It's great too!
Delicious!
Yes, it's good.
It's really good.
It's good, right?
You know what I mean?
It's made of candy, by the way.
Yum.
It's delicious.
You serve it with soy milk? No, I'm sure it's delicious.
Isn't fine juice supposed to taste like this too?
If you want to drink it, it's Shake Wasserloo! If you still want to drink, it will be Shake Wasserloo!
I had the coconut sata andagi and fine juice!
I have plain and drag hawk!
I also had a coconut sata andagi and a shake wassailoo!
It's super Okinawa!
And coconut and fine juice!
Cheers!
Delicious!
It's really good!
Bon appétit!
Delicious
If there is betta chee betta chee, I'll eat it warm.
That's right, it's too good!
I'll have a hot one.
Sweet?
It's better when it's warm.
It's delicious.
It's good.
Sounds a little different.
Same sound.
Thanks, but it sounds the same.
I can't see it.
Oh, it's not the same anymore.
I see it.
What am I supposed to do?
I'm doing my best to carry it. I'm doing my best to carry it.
Oh, it smells so good!
Nó.
What's this?
It's soft.
What is it?
It's delicious.
It tastes like curry.
By the way, it feels good to start with your arm.
Oh, you just did.
Sweets.
Sisa, you're so cute.
But I knew you'd want to put it in there.
I'm sure you'll get it.
It's Okinawan, so it's a sisa.
It's kind of Okinawan.
I wanted to show a little bit of the Okinawan atmosphere.
That's why the airplane
And some kind of palm hair.
And the sisa.
But also some kind of puppet
I'd like to put that in there.
So, yellow from my side
It's taking you a long time to choose, Misaki.
What's your pema?
I thought the dolphins were too cute.
The dolphins are the star of the show.
Look at it.
How should I put it?
Um...You know what?
The way it's warped is different.
Let this be the star.
Match it up a little.
I'm still looking...
I'm looking for a gem.
What's the theme?
Um...
Like peace in the summer.
Peace?
There are a lot of them.
I didn't decide on a genre, I just picked it up and thought "summer peace".
Good luck!
What is your theme?
Pastry.
I'm not sure if it's a local one or a small one.
I wanted to choose a cherry blossom theme.
But I don't have any cherry blossoms, so I'm going to go with flowers for now.
But I want it to be Japanese.
I'm not sure...
It only has one wing.
It looks like it has two.
What's that?
Let's eat it.
What color?
The last name, the tree bean, LAM.
White bull.
I'm going to go make some tea.
Come here.
I'm going home.I'm going home.
It's done.
It's so cute.
How is it? How did you guys do?
It's great.
The front.
The circle has expanded.
Yeah, I know.
But it's dynamic.
It gives it a three-dimensional look.
It's so cute!
They're all so different from each other.
It looks good.
Basically, it's like a taste.
It's like their eyes are glowing.
It's true.
They're really glowing.
The basics look good
It's like Shi-San's eyes are shining.
It's like they're glowing.
Yes, it is.
I want to see it.
I see.
So...
Today we're in Okinawa in the west.
I've heard that there's a lot of eating going on.
I hear it's glowing.
Drinking and making
I had a fun experience
I had a lot of fun!I did.
It was fun.
It was awesome.
You made memories.
Really.
That's nice.
That's good.
Yeah, it's good.
Yes.
I'll come back to Okinawa.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
I will go to Okinawa next time.
See you again.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!